[
    {
        "question": "Can a Muslim woman remove her hijab in front of non Muslim women?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAaY1sbt3kO/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it important to move your lips during salah?",
        "answer": "Yes; if you don't, your prayer is invalid.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_gBqLQt-8j/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can a Muslim reject a Sahih Hadith?",
        "answer": "No, as it is a ijma (consensus) of the scholars that rejecting a statement of the Prophet SAW that was reported to be authentic makes one a Kaffir (disbeliever).",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "IslamQA.info (Grade #2)",
                "link": "https://islamqa.info/en/answers/115125/ruling-on-one-who-rejects-a-saheeh-hadith"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can we combine Dhuhr and Asr at Dhuhr time?",
        "answer": "Yes BUT you can only do that if there is a legitimate Islamic reason such as traveling or rain.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAbALDYNz6Y/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do non muslims also have angels on their shoulders recording their good and bad actions?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DADEYLuNApI/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Does sin block blessings?",
        "answer": "Yes, this is possible.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_fGOmUNz33/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can we recite dua from the Quran in sujood?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_NIgM8tFVU/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What to do when you miss Salah because of sleep or forgot to pray?",
        "answer": "You pray it as soon as you wake up or remember it.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_LSwqiNP30/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is the prayer valid if a cat lays on the prayer mat? Or, if I played with a cat after wudu, would the prayer be valid?",
        "answer": "No problem in both.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_Z-L6ct5lm/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I pray qiyamul layl by reciting Quran while watching it on my phone?",
        "answer": "Yes.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_kUxgsNJJX/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Does kissing a wife on her lips invalidate her wudu?",
        "answer": "No.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C_6UQj2NRjt/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can I close my eyes while listening to the Quran?",
        "answer": "Yes IF you're not praying or driving.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C__TBAwtyi3/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it shirk to salute to national flag or stand when national anthem is being played?",
        "answer": "Both are prohibited and imitating the disbelievers but it is not shirk.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAFjEeiNZkj/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is black mascara allowed for eyelashes?",
        "answer": "Yes, this is permissible as this is a form of beautification and not a dye for the hair.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAIoHBNNQ4s/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is double chin considered as awrah?",
        "answer": "Yes, for women.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAYiUN1tLS_/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can an ordinary person perform Ruqyah on themselves or others, or is it necessary to be an imam?",
        "answer": "The best ruqyah is the one you perform on yourself.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/DAb5VvKtAwU/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is smoking haram or makhrooh?",
        "answer": "It's haram.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C-w-sThNmxs/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Can we buy and sell cats?",
        "answer": "No, the price of cats is haram in Islam.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C-r9XYGt2IZ/"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it compulsory to renew your wudu for every salah, even when you're still in a state of wudu?",
        "answer": "No, it is not mandatory. However, you are rewarded whenever you do wudu.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C-j0nS5NKGn/"
            }
        ]
    }
    {
        "question": "What is the ruling on hanging up Quranic verses on walls?",
        "answer": "Not permissible, because it's disrespecting Allah's words as it was not sent for decorative purposes, and if hung up to ward off evil eye or black magic etc, this becomes shirk.",
        "sources": [
            {
                "grade": "Assim Al-Hakeem (Grade #3)",
                "link": "https://www.instagram.com/p/C-acLCotr1g/"
            }
        ]
    }
]
